Contact

kathrynlibuserrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kathrynlibuser-msn-rn-cnor-nhdpbc-274a8431 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Healthcare

Hospitals

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Japanese (Limited Working)

Certifications

BLS

NHDP-BC (National Healthcare Disaster Professional- Board Certified)

Certified Nurse Operative Room (CNOR)

Basic Certificate in Quality and Safety

National Response Framework, An Introduction IS-00800.b

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau Honors Society
Phi Alpha Theta Honors Society
President's List
Dean's Honors List
Order of Omega

Kathryn Libuser, MSN, RN, CNOR, NHDP-BC

Urgent Care Nurse Triage at Cedars-Sinai Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

Registered Nurse, MSN with 3 years of experience in an acute care setting. Recent experience working as a OR Circulating Nurse in an acute care hospital. 5+ years in Perioperative Services, 3+ years of PACU, 1+ years in Medical Surgical/Telemetry Nursing, 2 years of case management and 3 months in ICU. Board Certified CNOR and National Healthcare Disaster Professional (NHD-BC).

Graduated from University of Arizona's MSN program in Clinical Systems Leadership April 2017

Specialties: Operating Room, Peri-Operative, Medical Surgical, Telemetry, Leadership, School Nursing, Case Management, Registered Nurse, Public Health Nursing

Experience

Triage for Covid-19

Cedars-Sinai Urgent Care Nurse April 2020 - Present (2 months)

Medely
Registered Nurse
December 2019 - Present (6 months)
Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

UCLA Health
Periop Travel RN
October 2019 - April 2020 (7 months)

Providence St. Joseph Health OR RN

April 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Tarzana, California

Cedars-Sinai Kerlan-Jobe Institute OR RN

January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

UCLA Health

RN Radiation Oncology and Perioperative Brachytherapy January 2017 - January 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Los Angeles, California

Brachytherapy nurse in the perioperative setting of the radiation oncology department. Work includes: pre-op patients for surgery; circulating in the OR during brachy implant surgery; recovery of patients in PACU; patient education in the radiation oncology clinic for ambulatory unit appointments.

La Peer Health Systems

1 year 3 months

Operating Room Circulating RN July 2016 - April 2017 (10 months)

Beverly Hills

Perioperative Nurse

February 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 3 months)

Beverly Hills

PACU and OR

Saint Francis Medical Center Surgery Center Registered Nurse June 2015 - February 2016 (9 months)

Lynwood, California

Pre-Op, Phase II Post-Op

Prep For Success, (Formerly Options For Youth)

School Nurse

December 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 1 month)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Case Management, Vision and Hearing Screenings, Physical Assessments etc.

Alta Hospitals System, LLC: Norwalk Community Hospital Medical Surgical/Telemetry Registered Nurse August 2014 - June 2015 (11 months)

Norwalk, California

Medical Surgical, Telemetry Acute Care Nursing

Universal Home Care
Nurse Field Supervisor and Pediatrics Case Manager
November 2013 - May 2015 (1 year 7 months)
Los Angeles

Home Visits, Nursing Assessments, Field Supervision of LVNs, and CNAs, Case Management of Pediatrics

Kindred Healthcare RN Case Manager February 2014 - September 2014 (8 months)

Community Hospital Long Beach 9 months

Telemetry Registered Nurse September 2013 - November 2013 (3 months) Long Beach, California

ICU Registered Nurse July 2013 - September 2013 (3 months) Long Beach, California

Outpatient Surgery, Perioperative Services March 2013 - July 2013 (5 months) Community Hospital Long Beach

Education

University of Arizona

Doctor of Nursing Practice , Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2020 - 2024)

University of Arizona

Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing · (2015 - 2017)

West Coast University-Orange County
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

Page 3 of 4

California State University-Long Beach
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), American/United States Studies/
Civilization · (2006 - 2012)

Culver City High School High School Diploma, General Studies · (2002 - 2006)